<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ML on d-xa tech blog</title><link>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/tags/ml/</link><description>Recent content in ML on d-xa tech blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/tags/ml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure Functions</title><link>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-azure_functions/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-azure_functions/</guid><description>Azure Functions Data Preparation Phase Model Building Phase Deployment Phase</description></item><item><title>ML Phases</title><link>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-ml_phases/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-ml_phases/</guid><description>Phases The process of building Machine Learning solutions is commonly divded into three phases: 1. data preparation, 2. model building, 3. deployment.
problem of clear definitions trend, competition, not tied to specific industry every company is a software company quote data is the new oil quote Data Preparation Phase Model Building Phase Deployment Phase</description></item><item><title>MLOps Design Patterns</title><link>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-mlops_design_patterns/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-mlops_design_patterns/</guid><description>Design Patterns CaaS ​
Container as a Service (CaaS) is a helpful pattern for MLOps because it allows developers to work on an ML microservice on their desktop or in a cloud editor and then shares it with other developers or the public via a docker pull command. Further, many cloud platforms offer high-level PaaS (Platform as a Service) solutions to deploy containerized projects. MLOps Platform All cloud providers have deeply integrated ​</description></item><item><title>What is Data Science</title><link>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-what_is_data_science-copy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://d-xa.github.io/tech-blog/wip/wip-what_is_data_science-copy/</guid><description>Data Science What is Data Science
Data Science (research vs. applied ..) Deep Learning, Machine Learning, Artificial Intelligence Statistical Learning, Pattern Recognition, Data Mining Descriptive, Advanced, Prescriptive Analytics etc. Data Preparation Phase Model Building Phase Deployment Phase</description></item></channel></rss>